# Zoltan Almodo Product, UI/UX Designer / Front-End developer

zoltanalmodo@gmail.com

## Github Portfolio

## **Profile**

I enjoy solving problems, enthusiastic about programming and learning new technologies.

My Education and experience in Product Design, Design Management and Visual Communications allow me to work closely with designers and design assets, to understand and modify UI/UX, communication and business strategies.

#### **Tech Skills:**

HTML5, CSS3, Less CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, React, Redux, React-Native, Reactstrap, Bootstrap, Node.js, Git / Github, MySQL, CSV

#### **Design Skills:**

Prototyping, Wireframing, UX/UI design, Adobe Photoshop / Illustrator / Xd / After Effects , Lotti, Figma, Google Material Design, IBM Carbon Design System, Microsoft Fluent, Apple Design - Human Interface Guidelines, Airbnb - Design Language System, Airbnb - Lottie, Uber Design System, Atomic Design System, Bootstrap, Reactstrap

# **Professional Experience:**

Overheard Deals: Designer, Web App Developer: 2019 - 2020

Web App-development, Mobile Application design, UI/UX design, Graphic design, data structure development, Qr code read function, Javascript / CSS animations.

Using: Figma, Photoshop, HTML, CSS, Javascript, React-Native, Axios, Mongo DB.

Download for => iOS / Android

Truckrefunds.com: Designer, Web Developer: 2019 - 2020

Web-development, UI/UX design, Graphic design.

Javascript, HTML, CSS, HubSpot CMS and Shopify ecommerce platform.

https://truckrefunds.com https://truckcartelrefunds.com

Purpose Group: Designer, Web Developer: 2018 - 2020

Web-application-development, UI/UX design, Graphic design.

Javascript, React, HTML, CSS.

Purpose-Group-webapp: Javascript, React, HTML, CSS

https://www.purposegroup.co.uk/ and https://www.manyhandslondon.co.uk/

https://purpose-react-app.herokuapp.com/

Please allow a few moments for the server to load...

**hSo:** Graphic Designer: permanent contract 2018 Graphic design, Web design, Online / Printed + Internal document design HTML, CSS, Photoshop, Illustrator

**Doode Disco (React.js side project):** Project for fun and to learn new technologies. 2018 React, Javascript, npm, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, HTML, CSS / Less CSS <a href="https://zoltan-kodflix-ddisco-app.herokuapp.com/">https://zoltan-kodflix-ddisco-app.herokuapp.com/</a>
Please allow a few moments for the server to load...

Jamseek: Progressive Web App. 2018
Graphic design, UI/UX design,
Photoshop, Illustrator, HTML, CSS, JavaScript
https://www.jamseekapp.co.uk/en/index.php

NNC No Name Corporation: Progressive Web App. 2017 Branding - Logo / Graphic design, UI/UX design Photoshop, Illustrator

**BNSC Logo design:** 2017 Branding - Logo / Graphic design Photoshop, Illustrator

Anuka Kid e-Commerce: 2017

Overall design and programming using Shopify.

Custom theme add-ons, added extra functionalities, custom Contact form, Card payment, Google Analytics.

HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript

<a href="https://anukakid.com/">https://anukakid.com/</a>

Andrea Ovari textile designer: 2017
Website design and programming
HTML, CSS, jQuery, Javascript (responsive, hand-coded)
<a href="http://www.ovariandrea.hu/">http://www.ovariandrea.hu/</a>

**OneDeko Ltd. London** - Web Designer eCommerce 2009 - 2017 Web-design, Web-shop design, Web-shop maintenance, Graphic design, online promotions. Prestashop, HTML, CSS, MySQL, CSV, jQuery. https://twitter.com/onedeko?lang=en

Philos Laboratories Hungary - Computer Games Graphic Design Lead 2000 March - 2002 July

- computer game graphic designer/concept artist / GUI designer
- leader of a five-person team, ensuring the quality of final products
- 2d and 3d characters + level concept design, graphical user interface design.

Using 2d and 3d software packages: Photoshop, Illustrator, 3ds Max.

## Other:

**Random Phrase Generator:** Javascript, HTML, CSS, DOM manipulation https://codepen.io/zoltanalmodo/pen/oMymYx

Yarimaki - Clothing Label 2008 - 2016

Art direction - branding - graphic design

Web-design, fashion design, Web-shop maintenance, label management, online promotions.

Using: Photoshop, Illustrator, HTML, CSS, MySQL, CSV, jQuery, Wordpress.

https://twitter.com/onedeko?lang=en

# **Education:**

KODIRI: Full-stack / React web-developer FreeCodeCamp: JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, React MOME University of Design Budapest: MA in Design Management 1997-2004 Master of Arts in Product Design 1996-2002 EVENTUS: Computer Graphic design 1995-1996

**Meetup groups:** Time to React, Kodiri London, Codecademy London, Js Monthly, JavaScript London, React London